<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="https://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="https://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="https://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="https://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="https://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blog by Branditechture</title>
	<atom:link href="https://localhost/branditechture/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://branditechture.com</link>
	<description>The Official Branditechture Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:43:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/favicon-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Blog by Branditechture</title>
	<link>https://branditechture.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>What is Abeg Naira? And How Does it Measure Up To The Naira?</title>
		<link>https://branditechture.com/what-is-abeg-naira/</link>
					<comments>https://branditechture.com/what-is-abeg-naira/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chukwudi Favour]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 22:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Brand Talks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://branditechture.com/?p=192</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Abeg is leveraging well its sponsorship deal with the Big Brother Naija Season 6: Shine Ya Eye. The Abeg Naira is the official in-house currency of the housemates.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/what-is-abeg-naira/">What is Abeg Naira? And How Does it Measure Up To The Naira?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<pre class="wp-block-preformatted"><strong><span class="has-inline-color has-luminous-vivid-orange-color">TLDR;</span></strong>
With a potential viewing and followership of over 12 million Africans daily and over 87% of that crowd being between 18 &amp; 35 years of age, the <strong>Big Brother Season 6; Shine Ya Eye</strong> is definitely a humongous publicity opportunity. An opportunity <strong><em>Abeg</em></strong> is leveraging well through its sponsorship deal with the platform. So well, the <strong><em>Abeg Naira</em></strong> is the official in-house currency of the housemates; that’s what they spend.</pre>



<p>It’s being scientifically proven that you remember names, better and more aptly than you do numbers.</p>



<p>Now, which fintech platform is utilizing this proven scientific fact for the good of their users?</p>



<p><strong><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-purple-color">Abeg!</span></strong></p>



<p>It’s the sixth season of the biggest reality TV show on the African continent right now, and there’s more mind-blowing gist than the usual in-house fights, love, and heartbreak and betrayal stories. And for the first time, the spotlight is shared by the sponsors (it’s usually all about the housemates only).</p>



<p>This sponsor is <strong><em>Abeg</em></strong>.</p>



<p>Wait, wait, wait, what?!</p>



<p>Okay, let me fill you in from the beginning.</p>



<p>In a land of myth and a time of…scratch that!</p>



<h2 id="h-what-is-1-abeg-naira-in-naira">What is 1 Abeg Naira in Naira?</h2>



<p>This is a question on the lips of many — especially those who are just new to the show. Now, let&#8217;s settle it; The Abeg Naira is a currency that only has an intrinsic value in the Big Brother House. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-video aligncenter"><video controls src="https://github.com/branditechture/branditechture.github.io/raw/master/static-assets/IMG_5512.mp4"></video><figcaption>Big Brother Housemate, Cross counting his Abeg Nairas.</figcaption></figure>



<p>Based on the terms of the 2bn Naira sponsorship deal, the Abeg Naira is the only supported currency in the Big Brother House, and it was designed to be used to purchase items by the Big Brother Season 6 Housemates. </p>



<p>Nice brand awareness strategy, I&#8217;d say.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-video aligncenter"><video controls src="https://github.com/branditechture/branditechture.github.io/raw/master/static-assets/IMG_5513.mp4"></video><figcaption>The Housemates doing some shopping with their Abeg Naira</figcaption></figure>



<p>Abeg Nairas cannot be exhanged with fiat currency, so there is no basis of comparison with the Nigerian Naira. Abeg Naira has to be earned by the housemates via rewards from sponsored tasks, thus effectively making some housemates richer than others.  </p>



<p>As for how much 1 Abeg Naira is valued against the Naira, you’d be asking the wrong question. </p>



<p>The phrase &#8220;Abeg Naira&#8221; may however see a subsequent use and popular adoption after the show is over, but that’d be something to definitely watch out for (who knows what cofounders Muheez Akanni and Dare Adekoya are up to?). </p>



<h2 id="h-what-inspired-the-abeg-app">What inspired the abeg app?</h2>



<p>Founded in 2019, Abeg Technologies is a team of vibrant youngsters led by the 26 year old <strong>Dare Adekoya;</strong> a talented product developer who designed the Abeg app as a response to a tweet by <strong><em>Asemota,</em></strong> sent to him by his friend <strong><em>Early Attoh</em></strong> on Dec 30, 2018, which read;</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>“I think one should build an app in Nigeria similar to $Cash and call it $Abeg. Bambiala culture is international.”</p><cite><strong>— Asemota</strong></cite></blockquote>



<p>According to Dare, he just wanted to quickly flex his design skills and do something badass with the Abeg idea. The plan was to post it hoping it could trend. So, he started working on the mini task, but unplanned, he fell in love with the logo and the rest is as we see, is unfolding.</p>



<p>Abeg App offers an alternative to bank transactions, which are usually besieged by several network issues and very importantly, exterminates the need for account numbers or any other details that usually proves difficult to remember for most folks. Yes. The Abeg app uses usernames known as abegtags instead of account numbers. The only information required to sign up on the platform, is the phone number integrated with the user’s preregistered Bank Verification Number (BVN).</p>



<p>Making the younger demographics of the country its target market, the Abeg app has a user-friendly interface that the average Nigerian youth will relate to easily with the integration of the colloquial phrase used to beg for favors; <em><strong>“Abeg”</strong></em>. </p>



<p>In the same vein, Abeg allows users to gift their friends’ money, organize giveaways for their followers, conduct fundraisers and earn approval badges and score points for their display of generosity. The app also adopts an extensive use of emojis and sticker features to gain the interest of the younger demographic.</p>



<p>As amazing as this app seems, Abeg is not the first fintech in the Nigerian market — There is already a domineering competition in the country and in the African tech market: <strong>Paga App</strong> with over 15.8M users as of June 2020, <strong>Cowrywise, </strong>handling over 220,000 users as of January 2021, <strong>Paystack</strong> serving over 60,000 users as of October 2020 and <strong>Kuda Bank,</strong> who just rounded up a successful series B serving over 1.4M users as of July 2021. However, Abeg App now has now implemented a marketing strategy that none of these fintech companies have used: <strong>Big Brother Season 6; Shine Ya Eye.</strong></p>



<h2>Headline Sponsorship </h2>



<p><strong>Abeg</strong>&nbsp;is the <strong><a class="extlink" href="https://africamagic.dstv.com/show/big-brother-naija/news/multichoice-unveils-abeg-as-s6-headline-sponsor-bbnaija/news" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Headline Sponsor</a></strong> of Big Brother Naija Season 6 while the Associate Sponsor is&nbsp;<strong>PATRICIA.</strong></p>



<p>Rumor has it that <strong>PATRICIA</strong> paid about 1 Billion Naira whilst <strong>Abeg</strong> paid a whooping 2 Billion Naira (no, not Abeg Naira; actual Naira).</p>



<p>As such, a host of other brands including <em><strong>Payporte</strong></em>, <strong><em>Pepsi</em></strong> and <strong><em>Heritage Bank</em></strong> amongst others, dive into the sponsorship opportunities on Big Brother Season 6, to educate the public about their products/services. </p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="600" height="1024" src="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/BB-Naija-Season-6-Sponsorship-Costs-Benefits-600x1024.png" alt="BB Naija Season 6 Sponsorship Costs Benefits" class="wp-image-193" srcset="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/BB-Naija-Season-6-Sponsorship-Costs-Benefits-600x1024.png 600w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/BB-Naija-Season-6-Sponsorship-Costs-Benefits-176x300.png 176w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/BB-Naija-Season-6-Sponsorship-Costs-Benefits.png 683w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /><figcaption>BB Naija Season 6 Sponsorship Costs Benefits</figcaption></figure></div>



<p>Last year, Betway was rumored to have paid over 1Bn Naira in total sponsorship money for the 2020 edition tagged <strong>Big Brother Season 5; Lockdown</strong>.</p>



<p>But for a startup that’s less than 3 years old, the headline sponsorship for the Big Brother Naija season 6, <strong>Abeg</strong>, has left many to wonder about the brand’s revenue generation strategies, the product, and its co-founders.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/what-is-abeg-naira/">What is Abeg Naira? And How Does it Measure Up To The Naira?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://branditechture.com/what-is-abeg-naira/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		<enclosure url="https://github.com/branditechture/branditechture.github.io/raw/master/static-assets/IMG_5512.mp4" length="173" type="video/mp4" />
<enclosure url="https://github.com/branditechture/branditechture.github.io/raw/master/static-assets/IMG_5513.mp4" length="173" type="video/mp4" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Handle Clients That Won&#8217;t Pay Your Balance</title>
		<link>https://branditechture.com/how-to-handle-clients-that-wont-pay-your-balance/</link>
					<comments>https://branditechture.com/how-to-handle-clients-that-wont-pay-your-balance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yusuf Odukoya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 16:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Web Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://branditechture.com/?p=169</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This article would help you to better manage stubborn clients who do not always want to pay your balance. I'll be very brief with my points but I'll try to make them as helpful as I can. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/how-to-handle-clients-that-wont-pay-your-balance/">How To Handle Clients That Won&#8217;t Pay Your Balance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="720" height="709" src="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Sad-Pablo-Escobar.jpeg" alt="Sad Pablo Escobar" class="wp-image-174" srcset="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Sad-Pablo-Escobar.jpeg 720w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Sad-Pablo-Escobar-300x295.jpeg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /><figcaption>MEME: Freelancer Waiting for payment after submitting work.</figcaption></figure></div>



<p>This article would help you to better manage stubborn clients who do not always want to pay your balance. I&#8217;ll be very brief with my points but I&#8217;ll try to make them as helpful as I can. </p>



<p>I brought this up because I have faced a series of challenges like this in the past, so I thought it&#8217;ll be an interesting discussion, especially for entry-level website designers and developers who seem to be quite inexperienced with the business side of website development.</p>



<p>First off, here are some of the crucial things you should put in place when starting a website design business. </p>



<ol><li>An invoicing system (a.k.a bookkeeping system) with auto-remind feature. </li><li>A business logo, website and corporate email address. </li><li>Basic business sense. </li></ol>



<p>Now let&#8217;s start. </p>



<h2 id="h-1-have-a-payment-policy-and-stand-firm-by-it">1. Have a Payment Policy and stand firm by it.</h2>



<p>You&#8217;ll lose some clients and that&#8217;s okay &#8211; Put a very brief summary of this payment policy (or Payment Terms) on your invoice, alongside your banking details. Also ensure that every invoice you send has a due date.</p>



<p>See the example below; </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="583" src="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-10.06.06-PM-1024x583.png" alt="Screen Shot 2021 08 16 at 10.06.06 PM" class="wp-image-185" srcset="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-10.06.06-PM-1024x583.png 1024w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-10.06.06-PM-300x171.png 300w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-10.06.06-PM-768x437.png 768w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-10.06.06-PM-1536x874.png 1536w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-10.06.06-PM.png 1624w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption>Sample Invoice with payment notes/terms.</figcaption></figure>



<h2>2. Write and pubish your Terms of Service </h2>



<p>Create and publish your Terms of Service (ToS) on a dedicated page on your website. You&#8217;ll need to let your client know that by using your service, they&#8217;ve accepted your <strong>Terms of Use</strong>. You may need to redirect them to this ToS page as a reference when they default or abuse those terms. </p>



<p>For your inspiration, <a class="extlink" href="https://branditechture.agency/terms-of-service/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">here is an example.</a> </p>



<h2>3. Declare a Grace Period </h2>



<p>A Grace Period is as important to the client as your balance is to you. A grace period is basically a period in which your customer is allowed to delay payment beyond the agreed due date. During this period, no late fees are charged and the website can still be left to work fully. This period is also an opportunity for you to get a little bit closer to your client in order to show them that you are concerned about their unresponsiveness. I personally give a grace period between 7 and 14 days. </p>



<p>Depending on the client&#8217;s attitude, after the Grace period elapses, you may want to charge them an additional 1% of the balance every day until they make their payment. This can be termed as a <strong>&#8220;Late Fee&#8221;</strong>, which is payable on top of the balance due. But you may keep yours simple and not charge the Late Fee. </p>



<h2>4. Notify them at every stage of their billing cycle. </h2>



<p>Expectedly, every invoice should have a due date appended to it. The due date is the &#8220;maximum date&#8221; when an invoice is expected to be settled.</p>



<p>It is important that you notify the customer at every stage of the billing cycle viz; Due date, grace period and restrictions. This is where invoice auto-reminders can help. You can either schedule the reminders to automatically fire, for example,<em> 3 days before the due date, <em>7 days after the due date,</em></em> <em>etc</em>, or you can do it manually. </p>



<p>I sometimes do mine manually because I love to personalize my tone when communicating with clients. You know,  not all clients are the same. </p>



<pre class="wp-block-preformatted">TIP: For invoices and reminders, use <em>a</em> mail address like billing@yourwebsite.com or accounting@yourwebsite.com.</pre>



<h2>5. Finally, impose a restriction on their website </h2>



<p>If all your due date reminders and grace period alert are ignored, you should now send them a final email ( or WhatsApp message ) asking about their wellbeing whilst politely informing them that their Grace period has passed and their website has been restricted as a result. It is important to mention that this is their last notice and they may not recieve further alerts from you. </p>



<p>Now, here is the most important part; Do not send them further alerts or notifications after this final notice. I repeat, DO NOT send the customer further alerts after imposing this restriction on their website. Breaking this rule would not only make you look beggy and pitiful, it would also dilute the efficacy of the restriction. </p>



<p>There are two ways to impose a restriction on their website; </p>



<h3>(i.) Use a modified index.html file</h3>



<p>Go to the website root folder and rename their index.php (as in WordPress-based websites) or index.html (found in static html websites) file to something like &#8220;indexxxx.php&#8221; or indexxx.html. The idea is to change the default index.html page. Next, upload this <strong>Website_Suspended.HTML</strong> file in their website root folder (usually named public_html) and rename the <meta charset="utf-8"><strong>Website_Suspended.HTML</strong> file to <strong><em>index.html. </em></strong></p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="640" src="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-9.23.08-PM-1024x640.png" alt="Screen Shot 2021 08 16 at 9.23.08 PM" class="wp-image-172" srcset="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-9.23.08-PM-1024x640.png 1024w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-9.23.08-PM-300x188.png 300w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-9.23.08-PM-768x480.png 768w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-9.23.08-PM-1536x960.png 1536w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-9.23.08-PM-2048x1280.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption>Screenshot &#8211; Account Suspended </figcaption></figure></div>



<p>Now, anytime they visit that website through the homepage, it&#8217;ll always serve the new index.html (which is the website suspended HTML page). </p>



<pre class="wp-block-preformatted">Click <a href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/branditechture/branditechture.github.io/master/Downloads/Website_Suspended.html" rel="nofollow"><strong>HERE</strong></a> to download the Website_Suspended.HTML file. 
<strong><span class="has-inline-color has-luminous-vivid-orange-color">TIP:</span></strong> You may need to manually save it (using Ctrl+S or CMD + S) if it opens as a text. Don't forget to rename the file to index.html before or after uploading.</pre>



<p>I like to use this method with non-techy clients because it&#8217;s very easy to undo once they settle their overdue balance. </p>



<p>The only disadvantage of this method is that the client would still be able to bypass the restriction by accessing their website via its sub directories, e.g https://website.com/subdir.</p>



<p>This should be seen as a soft restriction because it doesn&#8217;t harm their SEO as much, since other pages other than the homepage can still be accessed via the search engine result pages (or SERP). </p>



<h3>(ii.) Put the website in Coming Soon mode </h3>



<p>If you used WordPress, a much easier way would be to install a <strong>Coming Soon</strong> or <strong>Maintenance mode</strong> plugin, and then customize the message to display what you want. You can decide to put ads on it (But I guess that would be too extreme). </p>



<p>This method when used for long periods can send a bad signal to Google (due to the 503 Website Temporarily Unavailable HTTP header), thereby potentially hurting their search engine rankings.</p>



<p>After exhausting all the steps above, it is time to shift your focus to other jobs. </p>



<p>If you follow(ed) these tips religiously, I can assure you that your client would naturally &#8220;concede defeat&#8221; and chase after you with your full balance. It might take weeks or months, but they&#8217;ll almost certainly get back to you with your full balance. </p>



<p>Now, that&#8217;s cool and classy. <img loading="lazy" height="16" width="16" alt="😎" src="https://static.xx.fbcdn.net/images/emoji.php/v9/t22/2/16/1f60e.png"> You&#8217;ve handled a difficult issue the way big businesses do.</p>



<p>The best part? What transpired between you will usually not deter them from contacting you for other projects in the future. In fact, managing the situation using this strategy further proves that you are a professional.  </p>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/how-to-handle-clients-that-wont-pay-your-balance/">How To Handle Clients That Won&#8217;t Pay Your Balance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://branditechture.com/how-to-handle-clients-that-wont-pay-your-balance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why We Are Moving Our Blog Away From WordPress</title>
		<link>https://branditechture.com/why-we-are-moving-our-blog-away-from-wordpress/</link>
					<comments>https://branditechture.com/why-we-are-moving-our-blog-away-from-wordpress/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yusuf Odukoya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 12:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tech Talks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://branditechture.com/?p=17</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hello. Here’s Yusuf again. In this blog post, we would explain the reason behind our decision to move our website away from WordPress. Well, we didnt actually move from WordPress. We still use WP, but our website is now fully static. What led to this drastic decision? Well, I will tell you why. Two years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/why-we-are-moving-our-blog-away-from-wordpress/">Why We Are Moving Our Blog Away From WordPress</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hello. Here’s Yusuf again. In this blog post, we would explain the reason behind our decision to move our website away from WordPress.</p>



<p>Well, we didnt actually move from WordPress. We still use WP, but our website is now fully static.</p>



<p>What led to this drastic decision? Well, I will tell you why.</p>



<p>Two years ago, I created Branditechture Design Agency, a brand which was</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/why-we-are-moving-our-blog-away-from-wordpress/">Why We Are Moving Our Blog Away From WordPress</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://branditechture.com/why-we-are-moving-our-blog-away-from-wordpress/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Content Marketing is the future of Advertising</title>
		<link>https://branditechture.com/content-marketing-is-the-future-of-advertising/</link>
					<comments>https://branditechture.com/content-marketing-is-the-future-of-advertising/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yusuf Odukoya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 12:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://branditechture.com/?p=15</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This might sound like you’re very boring topic but I’m content marketing is actually the future of advertising. People might not tell you this but this is the ultimate budget silver. reasons why content marketing is the best for your business. &#160;content marketing is a new idea for most businesses and because of its long-term [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/content-marketing-is-the-future-of-advertising/">Content Marketing is the future of Advertising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>This might sound like you’re very boring topic but I’m content marketing is actually the future of advertising. People might not tell you this but this is the ultimate budget silver. reasons why content marketing is the best for your business.</p>



<p>&nbsp;content marketing is a new idea for most businesses and because of its long-term strategy and its low turnout a lot of businesses are unwilling to put in their time and effort in it. what makes a multibillion-dollar company?</p>



<p>&nbsp;that is the multibillion-dollar question.&nbsp; what if I told you that by just creating content your value can increase by more than 100% full stop content creation does not really cost you a huge sum of money</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/content-marketing-is-the-future-of-advertising/">Content Marketing is the future of Advertising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://branditechture.com/content-marketing-is-the-future-of-advertising/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Our employment process at Branditechture</title>
		<link>https://branditechture.com/our-employment-process-at-branditechture/</link>
					<comments>https://branditechture.com/our-employment-process-at-branditechture/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yusuf Odukoya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 12:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://branditechture.com/?p=13</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Our agency despite being a small company operates most similar to a large cooperation. And in this post, we will be giving you an insight on our recruitment and hiring process. Branditechture always seek the best talent and as a matter fact requires highly skilled professionals with with a fair educational qualification. I know some [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/our-employment-process-at-branditechture/">Our employment process at Branditechture</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Our agency despite being a small company operates most similar to a large cooperation. And in this post, we will be giving you an insight on our recruitment and hiring process. Branditechture always seek the best talent and as a matter fact requires highly skilled professionals with with a fair educational qualification.</p>



<p>I know some big companies who do not pass through due process during the hiring process employee. The disadvantage of this is that the employee the incoming employee is not completely imbibed in the company’s culture which is very dangerous to the future of that contract.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/our-employment-process-at-branditechture/">Our employment process at Branditechture</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://branditechture.com/our-employment-process-at-branditechture/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
