<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blog by Branditechture</title>
	<atom:link href="https://branditechture.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://branditechture.com</link>
	<description>The Official Branditechture Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 10:54:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/favicon-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Blog by Branditechture</title>
	<link>https://branditechture.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Nigerians Continue To Lament Incessant Defamation From Loan Apps</title>
		<link>https://branditechture.com/nigerians-continue-to-lament-incessant-defamation-from-loan-apps/</link>
					<comments>https://branditechture.com/nigerians-continue-to-lament-incessant-defamation-from-loan-apps/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yusuf Odukoya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 10:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tech Talks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://branditechture.com/?p=384</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The concept of being able to access collateral-free loans by just downloading an app seems incredible to many Nigerians — This reality has effectively made loan apps the most notable invention of the fastest-growing sector in the tech industry in Nigeria; Fintech. Loan apps like Branch, Carbon, Quick Check, FairMoney have started seeing competition from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/nigerians-continue-to-lament-incessant-defamation-from-loan-apps/">Nigerians Continue To Lament Incessant Defamation From Loan Apps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The concept of being able to access collateral-free loans by just downloading an app seems incredible to many Nigerians — This reality has effectively made loan apps the most notable invention of the fastest-growing sector in the tech industry in Nigeria; Fintech.</p>



<p>Loan apps like Branch, Carbon, Quick Check, FairMoney have started seeing competition from the likes of Okash, Soko Loan, 9Credit etc, as loan apps continue to make their way into the lives of more Nigerians. As a matter of fact, we have over 20 Nigerian loan apps on the Google Play Store.&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery columns-3 is-cropped"><ul class="blocks-gallery-grid"><li class="blocks-gallery-item"><figure><img loading="lazy" width="720" height="960" src="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/1.png" alt="1" data-id="393" data-full-url="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/1.png" data-link="https://branditechture.com/?attachment_id=393" class="wp-image-393" srcset="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/1.png 720w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/1-225x300.png 225w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></figure></li><li class="blocks-gallery-item"><figure><img loading="lazy" width="648" height="1024" src="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/2-648x1024.png" alt="2" data-id="394" data-full-url="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/2.png" data-link="https://branditechture.com/?attachment_id=394" class="wp-image-394" srcset="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/2-648x1024.png 648w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/2-190x300.png 190w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/2.png 720w" sizes="(max-width: 648px) 100vw, 648px" /></figure></li><li class="blocks-gallery-item"><figure><img loading="lazy" width="647" height="1024" src="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/3-647x1024.png" alt="3" data-id="395" data-full-url="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/3.png" data-link="https://branditechture.com/?attachment_id=395" class="wp-image-395" srcset="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/3-647x1024.png 647w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/3-190x300.png 190w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/3.png 720w" sizes="(max-width: 647px) 100vw, 647px" /></figure></li></ul></figure>



<p>While this is supposed to be a blessing to the common Nigerian citizen, a considerable majority of these tech firms have further plunged Nigerians into agony&nbsp; — not only financially, but through the defamation of character.&nbsp;</p>



<p>As a financial implication, some workers literally work for these “loan sharks”, no thanks to their super-high interest rate and short loan terms. The maximum loan term is usually 30 days, with interest rates as high as 30%! Or 1% per day.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 id="h-what-happens-at-the-end-of-your-loan-term">What happens at the end of your loan term?</h2>



<p>What happens at the end of your loan term depends on your loan status;</p>



<p><strong>(i.)</strong> If you have settled your loan by the end of your loan term, then you become <strong><em>a very close friend </em></strong>to them as your phones and emails would not stop ringing to their messages, telling you how <strong>you can quickly get another loan</strong>. This is how they make their money — At the expense of the mental health of Nigerians.&nbsp;</p>



<p>As short-term loan providers, they have failed to acknowledge a phenomenon known as <strong>Debt Addiction.</strong> Debt addiction is the compulsion to spend borrowed money on (unimportant) material things. It is also an urge to remain in debt by taking another loan as soon as the previous one is settled, regardless of the purpose.&nbsp;</p>



<p>I think these lending companies can do better by providing more information on loan management to their customers, either through a company blog or periodic newsletters. It is not every time you persuade people to come and take another loan. Unfortunately, I have yet to see a Nigerian money lender publicly educating their audience about debt management.</p>



<p>By providing helpful loan management resources, a lending company would automatically earn trust, respect and <a class="extlink" href="https://branditechture.agency/7-secrets-to-building-and-sustaining-brand-equity/">brand equity</a>. There is always dignity in acknowledging the mental health of your customers and I believe equipping them with such information will prove to be a great marketing strategy.&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>(ii.)</strong> If you have been unable to settle your loan, then be prepared to start getting threatening messages right from the due date (Although this depends on the loan app you borrowed from).&nbsp;</p>



<p>In spite of their humongous interest rates, these lending platforms take extreme measures in their process of debt recovery, causing harrassment, humiliation and irreparable defamation of character to loan defaulters — Whether your reasons for defaulting are of genuine concern or not, they will send libellous text messages to your contacts; brand you a wanted criminal who ran away with their company’s money. I consider this measure extreme because long lost friends, family members, bosses, colleagues at work, religious colleagues, and siblings all of whose contacts you have saved to your phone, would be bombarded with damaging messages about your personality.</p>



<p>In some cases, one is likely to be threatened personally about having their details sent to the Credit Bureau for blacklisting if they fail to make repayment on time. And even before the due date, there are constant phone calls that can be considered intrusive — all to remind defaulters to make payment.</p>



<p>Some borrowers have been pushed to the brink of suicide for being humiliated in such irrepairable ways.</p>



<p>According to reviews on the Google Play Store, Palm Credit (Easy Buy), Soko Loan, 9credit, and the likes also do these to their clients.&nbsp;</p>



<p>For Example, here are screenshots of the messages I got after one of my contacts borrowed money from an app called 9Credit and has failed to pay back after about three weeks after the due date. </p>



<p><strong><em>Click or tap to view full image</em></strong>;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery columns-2 is-cropped"><ul class="blocks-gallery-grid"><li class="blocks-gallery-item"><figure><a href="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screenie1-1.jpeg"><img loading="lazy" width="473" height="1024" src="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screenie1-1-473x1024.jpeg" alt="Screenie1 1" data-id="387" data-full-url="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screenie1-1.jpeg" data-link="https://branditechture.com/?attachment_id=387" class="wp-image-387" srcset="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screenie1-1-473x1024.jpeg 473w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screenie1-1-139x300.jpeg 139w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screenie1-1-768x1663.jpeg 768w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screenie1-1-709x1536.jpeg 709w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screenie1-1-946x2048.jpeg 946w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screenie1-1.jpeg 1125w" sizes="(max-width: 473px) 100vw, 473px" /></a></figure></li><li class="blocks-gallery-item"><figure><a href="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screenie2-1.jpeg"><img loading="lazy" width="826" height="1024" src="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screenie2-1-826x1024.jpeg" alt="Screenie2 1" data-id="388" data-full-url="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screenie2-1.jpeg" data-link="https://branditechture.com/?attachment_id=388" class="wp-image-388" srcset="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screenie2-1-826x1024.jpeg 826w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screenie2-1-242x300.jpeg 242w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screenie2-1-768x952.jpeg 768w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screenie2-1.jpeg 1125w" sizes="(max-width: 826px) 100vw, 826px" /></a></figure></li></ul></figure>



<h2>Other Real Life Experiences As Narrated By Nigerians</h2>



<p>According to a Nairaland user with the username <strong><em>Mrporanir</em>: </strong>&#8220;These guys go as far as impersonating barristers and lawyers just to make the situation look real. I blame android IS for not regulating them, you can never find such apps on IOS. I also blame the CBN for not regulating these loan sharks.&#8221;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="720" height="413" src="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Image-Credit-MrPoranir-Nairaland.jpeg" alt="Image Credit MrPoranir Nairaland" class="wp-image-390" srcset="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Image-Credit-MrPoranir-Nairaland.jpeg 720w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Image-Credit-MrPoranir-Nairaland-300x172.jpeg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /><figcaption>Image Credit: MrPoranir Nairaland</figcaption></figure>



<p>As you may notice in the second message from the screenshot above, they have gone a step further to involve a whole family.</p>



<p><strong>Another review by a disgruntled lender;</strong></p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p>😁😁 son-of-man sef tire oh..I just use vex pay, uninstall the useless pple.<br>Icash agent msg me for Whatsapp, say make I close eye pay early..<br>😁<br>..wetin man never see for loan shark hand</p><p></p><cite><meta charset="utf-8">Halogate, from Nairaland</cite></blockquote>



<p></p>



<p>Last week, a loan app called Sokoloan was fined 10 Million Naira by the Nigerian Information Technology Development Agency (or NITDA) for their persistent violation of privacy and misuse of users data. According to NITDA’s spokesperson, Hadiza Umar, ​​NITDA had sanctioned Soko Lending Company Limited for invasion of privacy.</p>



<p>This action was taken after receiving a series of complaints by Nigerians against the lending company for unauthorised disclosures, failure to protect customers’ personal data and defamation of character as well as carrying out the necessary due diligence as mandated in the Nigeria Data Protection Regulation (NDPR) which was published in 2019 by NITDA.&nbsp;</p>



<p>An excerpt of the statement reads as follows; “One of such complaints filed by <strong><em>Bloomgate Solicitors</em></strong> on behalf of its client, the data subject, was received on Monday, 11th November 2019. NITDA, as part of its due diligence process, commenced investigation over the alleged infractions of the provisions of the NDPR.”</p>



<p>“According to one of the complainants, when he failed to meet up with his repayment obligations due to insufficient credit in his account on the date the direct debit was to take effect, the company unilaterally sent privacy-invading messages to the complainant’s contacts.</p>



<p>“Investigation revealed that the complainant&#8217;s contacts who were neither parties to the loan transaction nor consented to the processing of their data have confirmed the receipt of such messages.”</p>



<p>It continues, “The agency made strident efforts to get Soko Loan to change the unethical practice but to no avail. After the agency’s investigation team secured a lien order on one of the company’s accounts by which it could come up with privacy-enhancing solutions for its business model, Soko Loan decided to rebrand and direct its customers to pay into its other business accounts.”</p>



<p>“The agency’s investigation further revealed that the company embeds trackers that share data with third parties inside its mobile application without providing users information about it or using the appropriate lawful basis.”</p>



<p>For the alleged breaches of privacy, NITDA thereby imposed a monetary sanction of 10 million Naira on Soko Loan.</p>



<h2 id="h-conclusion">Conclusion</h2>



<p>While your reasons for wanting a loan might be genuine, I would strongly recommend asking from your friends, family, colleagues or even your clients. By so doing, you&#8217;d not only avoid incurring huge interests on these loan apps, but you&#8217;d also have control over your personal data, thereby avoiding a full-blown defamation of your character by these loan sharks who charge as high as 30% &#8211; 50% for short-term loans.</p>



<p>Try to build a saving culture using an app like <strong><a class="extlink" href="https://www.piggyvest.com/?newref=1&amp;ref=4c48c54ec10419" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener sponsored nofollow">Piggyvest</a></strong> rather than spend everything that comes your way. This way, you can have some funds to fall back on in cases of emergencies rather than settle for loan sharks, default and face constant humiliation, harassment and threats.</p>



<p>I hope the CBN has plans to eliminate all the insanity currently going on in the fintech sector but till then, let&#8217;s thread safely.</p>



<p>Thank you for reading to this very end. Your comments are welcome.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/nigerians-continue-to-lament-incessant-defamation-from-loan-apps/">Nigerians Continue To Lament Incessant Defamation From Loan Apps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://branditechture.com/nigerians-continue-to-lament-incessant-defamation-from-loan-apps/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>2 Clever Tips That Will Deliver You From Quack Website Designers.</title>
		<link>https://branditechture.com/2-clever-tips-that-will-deliver-you-from-quack-website-designers/</link>
					<comments>https://branditechture.com/2-clever-tips-that-will-deliver-you-from-quack-website-designers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yusuf Odukoya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 06:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Tips]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://branditechture.com/?p=231</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There is a growing concern about the level of professionalism in the field of website design and it is becoming quite annoying. In the past, website design used to be an honourable profession and only a few could qualify as a web designer or developer. This is perhaps due to the barriers which were previously [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/2-clever-tips-that-will-deliver-you-from-quack-website-designers/">2 Clever Tips That Will Deliver You From Quack Website Designers.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>There is a growing concern about the level of professionalism in the field of website design and it is becoming quite annoying. In the past, website design used to be an honourable profession and only a few could qualify as a web designer or developer. This is perhaps due to the barriers which were previously associated with accessing web design tools, training, and certifications, but sadly, the industry is now oversaturated with quacks as any Monkey with a laptop and mobile internet access can easily pass for a website designer. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="768" src="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Angry-Woman-and-Cat-Meme-1024x768.jpg" alt="Angry Woman and Cat Meme" class="wp-image-232" srcset="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Angry-Woman-and-Cat-Meme-1024x768.jpg 1024w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Angry-Woman-and-Cat-Meme-300x225.jpg 300w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Angry-Woman-and-Cat-Meme-768x576.jpg 768w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Angry-Woman-and-Cat-Meme.jpg 1136w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><strong>What is the motivation behind this post?</strong></p>



<p>The overwhelming increase in the number of quack web designers on the World Wide Web has now made it very difficult for prospective website owners to avoid playing into the wrong hands. At least, 1 in every 5 website owners fall prey to a quack web designer. That&#8217;s not all — some prospective website owners have been tricked to part ways with their money in exchange for absolutely no value. To this end, I felt the need to do my own part by writing this piece.</p>



<p>I know it is impossible to eradicate this plague, but I want to believe that no one reads these tips and still ends up with a quack.</p>



<h2 id="h-1-request-their-portfolio-and-assess-their-own-website">1. Request their portfolio and assess their own website</h2>



<p>There is no gainsaying that this should be the first thing you should request from any web designer you are looking to hire. However, despite the fact that many people request a portfolio, they still fall prey to quack web designers because they forgot to request their own website. </p>



<p>The most important item on a web designer&#8217;s portfolio is arguably their own website. This is because a quack website designer can easily claim he built any website by just sending you a bunch of web links, but you&#8217;d be more accurate if you judge their capabilities by taking a look at their very own website.  </p>



<p>Take note of the following red flags;</p>



<ul><li>They don&#8217;t have a website.</li><li>They claim their website is under construction.</li><li>Their website loads very slowly.</li><li>Their website lacks content.</li><li>You see some dummy <strong><em>&#8220;Lorem Ipsum&#8221;</em></strong> texts scattered all over the place.</li><li>Unforgivable grammatical errors, both on and off their website.  </li></ul>



<h2 id="h-2-access-yourself-and-prepare-ahead">2. Access yourself and prepare ahead</h2>



<p>As a prospective website owner, it is also important for you to do a personal self-assessment as you are very likely to end up with a quack web designer if one or more of the reasons below apply to you;</p>



<ul><li>You don&#8217;t have an eye for good design.</li><li>You fail to discuss the performance side of your project.</li><li>Your budget is too low.</li><li>You overlook some or all of the red flags.</li></ul>



<p>It is quite simple — before embarking on a search for <a class="extlink" href="https://branditechture.agency/lets-build-your-website/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">a good web designer,</a> you should at least have some realistic expectations of what you wish to derive from the website in view; both aesthetically and functionally. You can achieve this by browsing through websites that share the same goal as yours, then noting down the things you like about them. You might also want to engage a reputable design-savvy friend to help you with making design-related decisions. </p>



<p>Take note of crucial things like the website&#8217;s <strong>Loading Speed,</strong> <strong>Content Structure and Hierarchy, Font Choices, Font Sizes and Styles, Colours, Logo Placement, Images e.t.c,</strong> and ensure it strikes a consistency with your brand or business, then ask if the web designer can help you achieve the same thing (by submitting it as a written brief). However, don&#8217;t take their word for it because they&#8217;ll most likely return an affirmative answer. </p>



<p>Now, here is the tricky part; You must verify their claim by cross-checking it against their portfolio (which you must have requested earlier) and look out for that same pattern in their previous works. <strong>Do previous works reflect their claims?</strong> If the answer is a big no, <strong><em>run for your life!</em></strong> But if the answer seems inconclusive, Still, <strong><em>run for your life</em></strong> (or proceed at your own risk). </p>



<p>It has to be a strong <strong>YES</strong>, which means all the website design projects featured on their portfolio must reflect their claims.</p>



<p></p>



<h2 id="h-conclusion">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Before you hire your next web designer, it is always a good idea to consider the two points above. They would go a long way in saving you from a potentially devastating disappointment. I have intentionally kept this article brief and straightforward so that it is very easy to follow, but if you have a tip that I have missed out, then share with us in the comments below. </p>



<p></p>



<p> </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/2-clever-tips-that-will-deliver-you-from-quack-website-designers/">2 Clever Tips That Will Deliver You From Quack Website Designers.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://branditechture.com/2-clever-tips-that-will-deliver-you-from-quack-website-designers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is Abeg Naira? And How Does it Measure Up To The Naira?</title>
		<link>https://branditechture.com/what-is-abeg-naira/</link>
					<comments>https://branditechture.com/what-is-abeg-naira/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chukwudi Favour]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 22:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Brand Talks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://branditechture.com/?p=192</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Abeg is leveraging well its sponsorship deal with the Big Brother Naija Season 6: Shine Ya Eye. The Abeg Naira is the official in-house currency of the housemates.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/what-is-abeg-naira/">What is Abeg Naira? And How Does it Measure Up To The Naira?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<pre class="wp-block-preformatted"><strong><span class="has-inline-color has-luminous-vivid-orange-color">TLDR;</span></strong>
With a potential viewing and followership of over 12 million Africans daily and over 87% of that crowd being between 18 &amp; 35 years of age, the <strong>Big Brother Season 6; Shine Ya Eye</strong> is definitely a humongous publicity opportunity. An opportunity <strong><em>Abeg</em></strong> is leveraging well through its sponsorship deal with the platform. So well, the <strong><em>Abeg Naira</em></strong> is the official in-house currency of the housemates; that’s what they spend.</pre>



<p>It’s being scientifically proven that you remember names, better and more aptly than you do numbers.</p>



<p>Now, which fintech platform is utilizing this proven scientific fact for the good of their users?</p>



<p><strong><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-purple-color">Abeg!</span></strong></p>



<p>It’s the sixth season of the biggest reality TV show on the African continent right now, and there’s more mind-blowing gist than the usual in-house fights, love, and heartbreak and betrayal stories. And for the first time, the spotlight is shared by the sponsors (it’s usually all about the housemates only).</p>



<p>This sponsor is <strong><em>Abeg</em></strong>.</p>



<p>Wait, wait, wait, what?!</p>



<p>Okay, let me fill you in from the beginning.</p>



<p>In a land of myth and a time of…scratch that!</p>



<h2 id="h-what-is-1-abeg-naira-in-naira">What is 1 Abeg Naira in Naira?</h2>



<p>This is a question on the lips of many — especially those who are just new to the show. Now, let&#8217;s settle it; The Abeg Naira is a currency that only has an intrinsic value in the Big Brother House. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-video aligncenter"><video controls src="https://github.com/branditechture/branditechture.github.io/raw/master/static-assets/IMG_5512.mp4"></video><figcaption>Big Brother Housemate, Cross counting his Abeg Nairas.</figcaption></figure>



<p>Based on the terms of the 2bn Naira sponsorship deal, the Abeg Naira is the only supported currency in the Big Brother House, and it was designed to be used to purchase items by the Big Brother Season 6 Housemates. </p>



<p>Nice brand awareness strategy, I&#8217;d say.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-video aligncenter"><video controls src="https://github.com/branditechture/branditechture.github.io/raw/master/static-assets/IMG_5513.mp4"></video><figcaption>The Housemates doing some shopping with their Abeg Naira</figcaption></figure>



<p>Abeg Nairas cannot be exhanged with fiat currency, so there is no basis of comparison with the Nigerian Naira. Abeg Naira has to be earned by the housemates via rewards from sponsored tasks, thus effectively making some housemates richer than others.  </p>



<p>As for how much 1 Abeg Naira is valued against the Naira, you’d be asking the wrong question. </p>



<p>The phrase &#8220;Abeg Naira&#8221; may however see a subsequent use and popular adoption after the show is over, but that’d be something to definitely watch out for (who knows what cofounders Muheez Akanni and Dare Adekoya are up to?). </p>



<h2 id="h-what-inspired-the-abeg-app">What inspired the abeg app?</h2>



<p>Founded in 2019, Abeg Technologies is a team of vibrant youngsters led by the 26 year old <strong>Dare Adekoya;</strong> a talented product developer who designed the Abeg app as a response to a tweet by <strong><em>Asemota,</em></strong> sent to him by his friend <strong><em>Early Attoh</em></strong> on Dec 30, 2018, which read;</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>“I think one should build an app in Nigeria similar to $Cash and call it $Abeg. Bambiala culture is international.”</p><cite><strong>— Asemota</strong></cite></blockquote>



<p>According to Dare, he just wanted to quickly flex his design skills and do something badass with the Abeg idea. The plan was to post it hoping it could trend. So, he started working on the mini task, but unplanned, he fell in love with the logo and the rest is as we see, is unfolding.</p>



<p>Abeg App offers an alternative to bank transactions, which are usually besieged by several network issues and very importantly, exterminates the need for account numbers or any other details that usually proves difficult to remember for most folks. Yes. The Abeg app uses usernames known as abegtags instead of account numbers. The only information required to sign up on the platform, is the phone number integrated with the user’s preregistered Bank Verification Number (BVN).</p>



<p>Making the younger demographics of the country its target market, the Abeg app has a user-friendly interface that the average Nigerian youth will relate to easily with the integration of the colloquial phrase used to beg for favors; <em><strong>“Abeg”</strong></em>. </p>



<p>In the same vein, Abeg allows users to gift their friends’ money, organize giveaways for their followers, conduct fundraisers and earn approval badges and score points for their display of generosity. The app also adopts an extensive use of emojis and sticker features to gain the interest of the younger demographic.</p>



<p>As amazing as this app seems, Abeg is not the first fintech in the Nigerian market — There is already a domineering competition in the country and in the African tech market: <strong>Paga App</strong> with over 15.8M users as of June 2020, <strong>Cowrywise, </strong>handling over 220,000 users as of January 2021, <strong>Paystack</strong> serving over 60,000 users as of October 2020 and <strong>Kuda Bank,</strong> who just rounded up a successful series B serving over 1.4M users as of July 2021. However, Abeg App now has now implemented a marketing strategy that none of these fintech companies have used: <strong>Big Brother Season 6; Shine Ya Eye.</strong></p>



<h2>Headline Sponsorship </h2>



<p><strong>Abeg</strong>&nbsp;is the <strong><a class="extlink" href="https://africamagic.dstv.com/show/big-brother-naija/news/multichoice-unveils-abeg-as-s6-headline-sponsor-bbnaija/news" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Headline Sponsor</a></strong> of Big Brother Naija Season 6 while the Associate Sponsor is&nbsp;<strong>PATRICIA.</strong></p>



<p>Rumor has it that <strong>PATRICIA</strong> paid about 1 Billion Naira whilst <strong>Abeg</strong> paid a whooping 2 Billion Naira (no, not Abeg Naira; actual Naira).</p>



<p>As such, a host of other brands including <em><strong>Payporte</strong></em>, <strong><em>Pepsi</em></strong> and <strong><em>Heritage Bank</em></strong> amongst others, dive into the sponsorship opportunities on Big Brother Season 6, to educate the public about their products/services. </p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="600" height="1024" src="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/BB-Naija-Season-6-Sponsorship-Costs-Benefits-600x1024.png" alt="BB Naija Season 6 Sponsorship Costs Benefits" class="wp-image-193" srcset="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/BB-Naija-Season-6-Sponsorship-Costs-Benefits-600x1024.png 600w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/BB-Naija-Season-6-Sponsorship-Costs-Benefits-176x300.png 176w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/BB-Naija-Season-6-Sponsorship-Costs-Benefits.png 683w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /><figcaption>BB Naija Season 6 Sponsorship Costs Benefits</figcaption></figure></div>



<p>Last year, Betway was rumored to have paid over 1Bn Naira in total sponsorship money for the 2020 edition tagged <strong>Big Brother Season 5; Lockdown</strong>.</p>



<p>But for a startup that’s less than 3 years old, the headline sponsorship for the Big Brother Naija season 6, <strong>Abeg</strong>, has left many to wonder about the brand’s revenue generation strategies, the product, and its co-founders.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/what-is-abeg-naira/">What is Abeg Naira? And How Does it Measure Up To The Naira?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://branditechture.com/what-is-abeg-naira/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		<enclosure url="https://github.com/branditechture/branditechture.github.io/raw/master/static-assets/IMG_5512.mp4" length="173" type="video/mp4" />
<enclosure url="https://github.com/branditechture/branditechture.github.io/raw/master/static-assets/IMG_5513.mp4" length="173" type="video/mp4" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Handle Clients That Won&#8217;t Pay Your Balance</title>
		<link>https://branditechture.com/how-to-handle-clients-that-wont-pay-your-balance/</link>
					<comments>https://branditechture.com/how-to-handle-clients-that-wont-pay-your-balance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yusuf Odukoya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 16:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Web Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://branditechture.com/?p=169</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This article would help you to better manage stubborn clients who do not always want to pay your balance. I'll be very brief with my points but I'll try to make them as helpful as I can. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/how-to-handle-clients-that-wont-pay-your-balance/">How To Handle Clients That Won&#8217;t Pay Your Balance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="720" height="709" src="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Sad-Pablo-Escobar.jpeg" alt="Sad Pablo Escobar" class="wp-image-174" srcset="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Sad-Pablo-Escobar.jpeg 720w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Sad-Pablo-Escobar-300x295.jpeg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /><figcaption>MEME: Freelancer Waiting for payment after submitting work.</figcaption></figure></div>



<p>This article would help you to better manage stubborn clients who do not always want to pay your balance. I&#8217;ll be very brief with my points but I&#8217;ll try to make them as helpful as I can. </p>



<p>I brought this up because I have faced a series of challenges like this in the past, so I thought it&#8217;ll be an interesting discussion, especially for entry-level website designers and developers who seem to be quite inexperienced with the business side of website development.</p>



<p>First off, here are some of the crucial things you should put in place when starting a website design business. </p>



<ol><li>An invoicing system (a.k.a bookkeeping system) with auto-remind feature. </li><li>A business logo, website and corporate email address. </li><li>Basic business sense. </li></ol>



<p>Now let&#8217;s start. </p>



<h2 id="h-1-have-a-payment-policy-and-stand-firm-by-it">1. Have a Payment Policy and stand firm by it.</h2>



<p>You&#8217;ll lose some clients and that&#8217;s okay &#8211; Put a very brief summary of this payment policy (or Payment Terms) on your invoice, alongside your banking details. Also ensure that every invoice you send has a due date.</p>



<p>See the example below; </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="583" src="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-10.06.06-PM-1024x583.png" alt="Screen Shot 2021 08 16 at 10.06.06 PM" class="wp-image-185" srcset="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-10.06.06-PM-1024x583.png 1024w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-10.06.06-PM-300x171.png 300w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-10.06.06-PM-768x437.png 768w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-10.06.06-PM-1536x874.png 1536w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-10.06.06-PM.png 1624w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption>Sample Invoice with payment notes/terms.</figcaption></figure>



<h2>2. Write and pubish your Terms of Service </h2>



<p>Create and publish your Terms of Service (ToS) on a dedicated page on your website. You&#8217;ll need to let your client know that by using your service, they&#8217;ve accepted your <strong>Terms of Use</strong>. You may need to redirect them to this ToS page as a reference when they default or abuse those terms. </p>



<p>For your inspiration, <a class="extlink" href="https://branditechture.agency/terms-of-service/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">here is an example.</a> </p>



<h2>3. Declare a Grace Period </h2>



<p>A Grace Period is as important to the client as your balance is to you. A grace period is basically a period in which your customer is allowed to delay payment beyond the agreed due date. During this period, no late fees are charged and the website can still be left to work fully. This period is also an opportunity for you to get a little bit closer to your client in order to show them that you are concerned about their unresponsiveness. I personally give a grace period between 7 and 14 days. </p>



<p>Depending on the client&#8217;s attitude, after the Grace period elapses, you may want to charge them an additional 1% of the balance every day until they make their payment. This can be termed as a <strong>&#8220;Late Fee&#8221;</strong>, which is payable on top of the balance due. But you may keep yours simple and not charge the Late Fee. </p>



<h2>4. Notify them at every stage of their billing cycle. </h2>



<p>Expectedly, every invoice should have a due date appended to it. The due date is the &#8220;maximum date&#8221; when an invoice is expected to be settled.</p>



<p>It is important that you notify the customer at every stage of the billing cycle viz; Due date, grace period and restrictions. This is where invoice auto-reminders can help. You can either schedule the reminders to automatically fire, for example,<em> 3 days before the due date, <em>7 days after the due date,</em></em> <em>etc</em>, or you can do it manually. </p>



<p>I sometimes do mine manually because I love to personalize my tone when communicating with clients. You know,  not all clients are the same. </p>



<pre class="wp-block-preformatted">TIP: For invoices and reminders, use <em>a</em> mail address like billing@yourwebsite.com or accounting@yourwebsite.com.</pre>



<h2>5. Finally, impose a restriction on their website </h2>



<p>If all your due date reminders and grace period alert are ignored, you should now send them a final email ( or WhatsApp message ) asking about their wellbeing whilst politely informing them that their Grace period has passed and their website has been restricted as a result. It is important to mention that this is their last notice and they may not recieve further alerts from you. </p>



<p>Now, here is the most important part; Do not send them further alerts or notifications after this final notice. I repeat, DO NOT send the customer further alerts after imposing this restriction on their website. Breaking this rule would not only make you look beggy and pitiful, it would also dilute the efficacy of the restriction. </p>



<p>There are two ways to impose a restriction on their website; </p>



<h3>(i.) Use a modified index.html file</h3>



<p>Go to the website root folder and rename their index.php (as in WordPress-based websites) or index.html (found in static html websites) file to something like &#8220;indexxxx.php&#8221; or indexxx.html. The idea is to change the default index.html page. Next, upload this <strong>Website_Suspended.HTML</strong> file in their website root folder (usually named public_html) and rename the <meta charset="utf-8"><strong>Website_Suspended.HTML</strong> file to <strong><em>index.html. </em></strong></p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="640" src="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-9.23.08-PM-1024x640.png" alt="Screen Shot 2021 08 16 at 9.23.08 PM" class="wp-image-172" srcset="https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-9.23.08-PM-1024x640.png 1024w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-9.23.08-PM-300x188.png 300w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-9.23.08-PM-768x480.png 768w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-9.23.08-PM-1536x960.png 1536w, https://branditechture.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Screen-Shot-2021-08-16-at-9.23.08-PM-2048x1280.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption>Screenshot &#8211; Account Suspended </figcaption></figure></div>



<p>Now, anytime they visit that website through the homepage, it&#8217;ll always serve the new index.html (which is the website suspended HTML page). </p>



<pre class="wp-block-preformatted">Click <a href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/branditechture/branditechture.github.io/master/Downloads/Website_Suspended.html" rel="nofollow"><strong>HERE</strong></a> to download the Website_Suspended.HTML file. 
<strong><span class="has-inline-color has-luminous-vivid-orange-color">TIP:</span></strong> You may need to manually save it (using Ctrl+S or CMD + S) if it opens as a text. Don't forget to rename the file to index.html before or after uploading.</pre>



<p>I like to use this method with non-techy clients because it&#8217;s very easy to undo once they settle their overdue balance. </p>



<p>The only disadvantage of this method is that the client would still be able to bypass the restriction by accessing their website via its sub directories, e.g https://website.com/subdir.</p>



<p>This should be seen as a soft restriction because it doesn&#8217;t harm their SEO as much, since other pages other than the homepage can still be accessed via the search engine result pages (or SERP). </p>



<h3>(ii.) Put the website in Coming Soon mode </h3>



<p>If you used WordPress, a much easier way would be to install a <strong>Coming Soon</strong> or <strong>Maintenance mode</strong> plugin, and then customize the message to display what you want. You can decide to put ads on it (But I guess that would be too extreme). </p>



<p>This method when used for long periods can send a bad signal to Google (due to the 503 Website Temporarily Unavailable HTTP header), thereby potentially hurting their search engine rankings.</p>



<p>After exhausting all the steps above, it is time to shift your focus to other jobs. </p>



<p>If you follow(ed) these tips religiously, I can assure you that your client would naturally &#8220;concede defeat&#8221; and chase after you with your full balance. It might take weeks or months, but they&#8217;ll almost certainly get back to you with your full balance. </p>



<p>Now, that&#8217;s cool and classy. <img loading="lazy" height="16" width="16" alt="😎" src="https://static.xx.fbcdn.net/images/emoji.php/v9/t22/2/16/1f60e.png"> You&#8217;ve handled a difficult issue the way big businesses do.</p>



<p>The best part? What transpired between you will usually not deter them from contacting you for other projects in the future. In fact, managing the situation using this strategy further proves that you are a professional.  </p>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/how-to-handle-clients-that-wont-pay-your-balance/">How To Handle Clients That Won&#8217;t Pay Your Balance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://branditechture.com/how-to-handle-clients-that-wont-pay-your-balance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why We Are Moving Our Blog Away From WordPress</title>
		<link>https://branditechture.com/why-we-are-moving-our-blog-away-from-wordpress/</link>
					<comments>https://branditechture.com/why-we-are-moving-our-blog-away-from-wordpress/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yusuf Odukoya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 12:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tech Talks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://branditechture.com/?p=17</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hello. Here’s Yusuf again. In this blog post, we would explain the reason behind our decision to move our website away from WordPress. Well, we didnt actually move from WordPress. We still use WP, but our website is now fully static. What led to this drastic decision? Well, I will tell you why. Two years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/why-we-are-moving-our-blog-away-from-wordpress/">Why We Are Moving Our Blog Away From WordPress</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hello. Here’s Yusuf again. In this blog post, we would explain the reason behind our decision to move our website away from WordPress.</p>



<p>Well, we didnt actually move from WordPress. We still use WP, but our website is now fully static.</p>



<p>What led to this drastic decision? Well, I will tell you why.</p>



<p>Two years ago, I created Branditechture Design Agency, a brand which was</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/why-we-are-moving-our-blog-away-from-wordpress/">Why We Are Moving Our Blog Away From WordPress</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://branditechture.com/why-we-are-moving-our-blog-away-from-wordpress/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Content Marketing is the future of Advertising</title>
		<link>https://branditechture.com/content-marketing-is-the-future-of-advertising/</link>
					<comments>https://branditechture.com/content-marketing-is-the-future-of-advertising/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yusuf Odukoya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 12:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://branditechture.com/?p=15</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This might sound like you’re very boring topic but I’m content marketing is actually the future of advertising. People might not tell you this but this is the ultimate budget silver. reasons why content marketing is the best for your business. &#160;content marketing is a new idea for most businesses and because of its long-term [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/content-marketing-is-the-future-of-advertising/">Content Marketing is the future of Advertising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>This might sound like you’re very boring topic but I’m content marketing is actually the future of advertising. People might not tell you this but this is the ultimate budget silver. reasons why content marketing is the best for your business.</p>



<p>&nbsp;content marketing is a new idea for most businesses and because of its long-term strategy and its low turnout a lot of businesses are unwilling to put in their time and effort in it. what makes a multibillion-dollar company?</p>



<p>&nbsp;that is the multibillion-dollar question.&nbsp; what if I told you that by just creating content your value can increase by more than 100% full stop content creation does not really cost you a huge sum of money</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/content-marketing-is-the-future-of-advertising/">Content Marketing is the future of Advertising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://branditechture.com/content-marketing-is-the-future-of-advertising/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Our employment process at Branditechture</title>
		<link>https://branditechture.com/our-employment-process-at-branditechture/</link>
					<comments>https://branditechture.com/our-employment-process-at-branditechture/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yusuf Odukoya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 12:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://branditechture.com/?p=13</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Our agency despite being a small company operates most similar to a large cooperation. And in this post, we will be giving you an insight on our recruitment and hiring process. Branditechture always seek the best talent and as a matter fact requires highly skilled professionals with with a fair educational qualification. I know some [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/our-employment-process-at-branditechture/">Our employment process at Branditechture</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Our agency despite being a small company operates most similar to a large cooperation. And in this post, we will be giving you an insight on our recruitment and hiring process. Branditechture always seek the best talent and as a matter fact requires highly skilled professionals with with a fair educational qualification.</p>



<p>I know some big companies who do not pass through due process during the hiring process employee. The disadvantage of this is that the employee the incoming employee is not completely imbibed in the company’s culture which is very dangerous to the future of that contract.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com/our-employment-process-at-branditechture/">Our employment process at Branditechture</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://branditechture.com">Blog by Branditechture</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://branditechture.com/our-employment-process-at-branditechture/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
