<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blog by Branditechture</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/branditechture/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../index.html</link>
	<description>The Official Branditechture Blog Where Topics Relating To Tech, Design and Branding Are Discussed</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 16:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8</generator>

<image>
	<url>./../wp-content/uploads/2021/08/favicon-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Blog by Branditechture</title>
	<link>./../index.html</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Why We Are Moving Our Blog Away From WordPress</title>
		<link>./../why-we-are-moving-our-blog-away-from-wordpress/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../why-we-are-moving-our-blog-away-from-wordpress/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yusuf Odukoya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 12:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tech Talks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../index.html?p=17</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hello. Here’s Yusuf again. In this blog post, we would explain the reason behind our decision to move our website away from WordPress. Well, we didnt actually move from WordPress. We still use WP, but our website is now fully static. What led to this drastic decision? Well, I will tell you why. Two years [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hello. Here’s Yusuf again. In this blog post, we would explain the reason behind our decision to move our website away from WordPress.</p>



<p>Well, we didnt actually move from WordPress. We still use WP, but our website is now fully static.</p>



<p>What led to this drastic decision? Well, I will tell you why.</p>



<p>Two years ago, I created Branditechture Design Agency, a brand which was</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../why-we-are-moving-our-blog-away-from-wordpress/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Content Marketing is the future of Advertising</title>
		<link>./../content-marketing-is-the-future-of-advertising/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../content-marketing-is-the-future-of-advertising/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yusuf Odukoya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 12:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../index.html?p=15</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This might sound like you’re very boring topic but I’m content marketing is actually the future of advertising. People might not tell you this but this is the ultimate budget silver. reasons why content marketing is the best for your business. &#160;content marketing is a new idea for most businesses and because of its long-term [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>This might sound like you’re very boring topic but I’m content marketing is actually the future of advertising. People might not tell you this but this is the ultimate budget silver. reasons why content marketing is the best for your business.</p>



<p>&nbsp;content marketing is a new idea for most businesses and because of its long-term strategy and its low turnout a lot of businesses are unwilling to put in their time and effort in it. what makes a multibillion-dollar company?</p>



<p>&nbsp;that is the multibillion-dollar question.&nbsp; what if I told you that by just creating content your value can increase by more than 100% full stop content creation does not really cost you a huge sum of money</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../content-marketing-is-the-future-of-advertising/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Our employment process at Branditechture</title>
		<link>./../our-employment-process-at-branditechture/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../our-employment-process-at-branditechture/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yusuf Odukoya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 12:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../index.html?p=13</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Our agency despite being a small company operates most similar to a large cooperation. And in this post, we will be giving you an insight on our recruitment and hiring process. Branditechture always seek the best talent and as a matter fact requires highly skilled professionals with with a fair educational qualification. I know some [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Our agency despite being a small company operates most similar to a large cooperation. And in this post, we will be giving you an insight on our recruitment and hiring process. Branditechture always seek the best talent and as a matter fact requires highly skilled professionals with with a fair educational qualification.</p>



<p>I know some big companies who do not pass through due process during the hiring process employee. The disadvantage of this is that the employee the incoming employee is not completely imbibed in the company’s culture which is very dangerous to the future of that contract.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../our-employment-process-at-branditechture/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
